发生了一起谋杀案
There was a murder.
他真的把他杀了
He really massacred him.
我不明白
I don't get this.
下面是一个十字架
And below that there's something like a cross.
我希望今晚就能签合同
I wish we could sign the contract tonight.
到目前为止，他一分钱也没付
He hasn't paid anything so far.
现在又让我们投资新的产业
And makes us get into a new investment.
银行的生存危在旦夕
The survival of our bank is at stake.
一切都按计划进行
Everything went as we agreed.
不，不是的
No, it's not.
诺维奇伯爵
Count Nowicki.
消失得无影无踪
Nowicki disappeared without a trace.
共产国际对什么都感兴趣
The Comintern is interested in everything.
尤其是你那个疯狂的组织
Especially since your crazy organization
一直在和法国人私下密谋
has been whispering to the French
如何在贝尔格莱德暗杀亚历山大国王
on how to kill King Alexander in the middle of Belgrade.
什么暗杀国王? ! 你在说什么？
What assassination of the king?! What are you talking about?
意思是今晚没有牌局，你留下
It means there's no game tonight. You stay.
经营地下赌场？这也体面吗？
And securing gambling sessions? That's fair, too?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
戈迪纳先生，你赶时间吗？
Mr. Godina, are you in a hurry?
乌斯塔沙
The Ustasha.
他为美国黑手党工作，乔洛维奇带他来的
He works for the American mafia, Djolovich brought him.
我可以为你提供马其顿最好的鸦片
So, I offer you Macedonian opium of the highest quality,
我控制着一切: 从生产
I control everything: from production,
到运输，再到机构
through transport, to institutions.
塔尼，你得帮帮我！
Tane, you have to help me!
你对阿瓦拉了如指掌
You know Avala like the back of your hand.
这里有一些隧道
There are some tunnels.
有一个入口可以直接通向纪念碑
There is one entrance that should lead straight to the monument.
那里真的埋了一个孩子吗？
Is it true that a child was buried there?
你请我来为一位默默无闻的英雄立碑
You invited me to make a monument to an unknown hero.
现在却连尸骨都没有
There are no bones from either the known or the unknown.
- 就在这儿 - 哪儿? ！
- It was here. - Where?!
在这些石头上，我肯定它就在这里！
On these stones. I'm sure it was here!
尸体在哪儿? ！
Where's the corpse?!
南斯拉夫王国边界 意大利 皮兰
PIRAN, ITALY THE KINGDOM OF YUGOSLAVIA BORDER
放松点，保加利亚人，我投降
Easy, Bulgarian, what's wrong? I give up.
操你妈的！
Fuck you!
如果我想的话我会操你妈的
Oh, I would fuck you if I wanted to.
在你注意到我之前，我可以杀了你一千次
I could have killed you a thousand times until you noticed me.
我们走
Let's go.
这是你的票
This is your ticket.
火车两小时后开，你去布达佩斯
The train leaves in two hours, you're going to Budapest
有个人在那里等你，他会给你更多的信息
a man is waiting for you there and will give further information.
去集中营? 就像乌斯塔莎招募的新兵？
To a camp? Like an Ustasha recruit?
可能吧
Probably.
老板没有通知我这件事
The boss did not inform me about it.
如果你认为我会在集中营里浪费时间
If you think I'm going to waste time in that camp,
你大错特错了
you're sorely mistaken.
你得和老板谈谈，我已经做了我该做的
You'll have to talk to boss about it, I've done my thing.
所以你只是个传话筒？
And you're some honest prankster?
差不多吧
Something like that.
再见，保加利亚人！
Bye, Bulgarian!
达米扬 · 哈吉 · 阿尔索夫？
Damyan Hadzi Arsov?
你是谁？
Who's asking?
丹尼洛 · 托马斯维奇，很高兴见到你
Danilo Tomasovich, nice to meet you.
你离家太远了，老乡
You're far from home, countryman.
我们是什么老乡？
What kind of countrymen are we?
南斯拉夫人
Southern Slavs.
亲兄弟，一个国家，三个名字
Blood brothers. One nation, three names.
你想从我这里得到什么？
What do you want from me?
首先，你要先感谢我救了你的命
Firstly, to thank me for saving your life.
不是什么特别的帮助，但还是谢谢你
Not a special favour, but thank you.
你可以为你的忘恩负义道歉
You could apologize for being ungrateful.
我不会向任何人道歉，什么事快说
I don't apologize to anyone. Shoot.
别跟我说第二遍
Don't tell me twice.
- 我带你去个安全的地方 - 这是什么？
- I'm taking you to a safe place. - What's this?
我们的新工作，海洛因
Our new job. Heroin.
巴尔干半岛的阴影 第二季 第三集
BLACK SUN SEASON 2 EPISODE 3
- 干嘛？- 别问
- What? - Don't ask what.
我们吃早饭吧
Let's have breakfast.
就来
I'm coming.
这算什么鸡蛋？天啊！你在这吃的都是什么...
What kind of eggs are these? Oh, God, what you eat here...
我去我的农民朋友那里拿一些，你会..
Let me bring some from my farmers and you'll...
- 你为什么不吃？- 我不能吃
- Why aren't you eating? - I can't.
但你却可以喝酒
But you can drink.
我不会让你变得像那些警察局的酒鬼
I won't let you become like those guys from Glavnjacha.
我不该让你离开警局
I shouldn't have let you out of Glavnjacha.
- 你? ! - 是的
- You?! - Me, yes.
阿里姆皮耶会在两个小时内把我放出来
Alimpiye would let me out in less than two hours.
你唯一能做的就是逮捕妓女和穷人
The only thing you can do is arrest whores and the poor.
阿里姆皮耶是做什么的？
What does Alimpiye do?
- 谁会去他的俱乐部？- 这个城市的所有人
- Who comes to his club? - The whole city.
有人提到日尔诺夫的谋杀案吗？
Does anyone mention the murder on Zhrnov?
没有，大家都在谈论亚塔汉贫民窟，你什么都没吃
No, just the Yataghan slum. You didn't eat anything.
- 亚塔汉贫民窟是怎么了？- 我不知道
- What's with Yataghan slum? - I don't know.
他们讨论要拆什么东西
They gather there to tear something down
然后要建造什么，我不太懂
and then to build something, I didn't understand.
- 帮我弄清楚 - 我试试
- Find it out for me. - I'll try.
不要尝试，一定要查清
Don't try. Do it.
不然呢？
Or what?
你又要逮捕我吗？
You're gonna arrest me again?
如果你认为我告诉你这些是因为我害怕你，那你就是个傻瓜
You're a fool if you think I'm telling you this because I'm afraid of you.
如果尼娜害怕，她就不会离开斯托拉茨
If Nina was scared, she wouldn't get out of Stolac.
你那个朋友呢...
What about that friend...
是谁把你从斯托拉茨弄出来，然后让修道士雇了你
Who got you out of Stolac and hired you at the Monk's place.
他怎么了？
What about him?
你告诉我关于每个人的事，但都不是关于他的
You tell me about everyone but not about him.
不重要
It doesn't matter.
我欠他太多了
I owe him a lot.
你把他藏起来了？
Are you hiding him?
你吃醋了吗？
Are you jealous?
不，我只是感兴趣
No, I'm just interested.
嘿，泽切维奇
Hey, Zechevich.
又发生了一起谋杀案
We have a new murder.
法院院长被杀害了
The president of the court was killed.
好的，在警局等我，我马上就来
Okay, wait for me at Glavnjacha. I'm coming soon.
这一刻终于到来了！
This moment has finally arrived!
你这个施瓦本（德国西南部）老公不错
This Swabian of yours is good.
是的，他很好，但他是施瓦本人
Yes, he's good. But he's Swabian.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed at all.
是的，你却变得更漂亮了
You have. You're even prettier.
好吧，如果是这样的话...让我们举杯吧
Well, if so... Let's make a toast.
不，我不喝酒
No, I don't drink.
- 你不喝酒？- 相信我
- You don't drink?! - Trust me.
我不信，给你
I don't. Here you go.
敬多年后的重逢
To the reunion, after all these years.
五年
Five.
你在计数？
You were counting?
我喜欢精确
I like to be accurate.
我们没有很多这样精确的东西
We don't have many of them available.
太糟糕了
Too bad...
这么多年来
For all those years.
真的? 为什么？
Really? Why?
- 我好想你 - 玛雅，拜托
- I missed you. - Oh, Maya, please.
你消失了五年
You disappear for five years,
无处可寻，在世界各地游荡
you're nowhere to be found, wander around the world,
结婚，然后你现在说你想念..
get married and then you really miss...
一个来自贝尔格莱德的酒鬼警察
a drunk cop from Belgrade.
饶了我吧，你为什么找我？
Give me a break. Why did you call me?
我想见你
I wanted to see you.
嗯，我有时也撒谎，但是我撒谎的技术比你高多了
Well, I lie sometimes too, but I do it much better than you.
塔尼，我真的很想你
Tane, I really missed you.
我渴望找到一个我真正信任的人
I longed for someone I could really trust.
你不相信任何人
You don't trust anyone.
你也是
Neither do you.
这就是为什么我们能理解彼此
That is why we feel and understand each other.
到底怎么回事？
What's going on?
我听说了一些可怕的事情
I've heard terrible things.
他们想刺杀我们的国王
They want to kill our king.
在这里，贝尔格莱德
Here, in Belgrade.
- 谁想杀他？- 我认为是...
- Who wants to kill him? - I thought...
乌斯塔沙和 IMRO，但事实证明，共产国际组织也参与其中
Ustashas and IMRO but it turns out the communists are also in the game,
好像也和图勒组织有关
it seems to have something to do with The Thules as well
还有穆斯塔法 · 戈卢比奇
And Mustapha Golubich
不知何故参与了这一切
is somehow involved in all that.
奥地利 维也纳
VIENNA, AUSTRIA
- 下午好，帕维里奇先生 - 下午好，克劳斯先生
- Good afternoon, Mr. Pavelich. - Good afternoon, Mr. Klaus.
抱歉，我迟到了，小姐...
Sorry I'm late. Miss...
说重点，帕维里奇先生
Get to the point, Mr. Pavelich.
你知道，我们在失败之后遇到了大麻烦..
You know, we're in big trouble after our failure...
失败？
Failure?
真是轻描淡写
That's an understatement.
意大利人
The Italians
最近对我们的事业没有任何同情心
aren't showing any empathy for our cause lately.
意料之中
That was to be expected.
我们正面临金融危机
We are facing a financial collapse.
人民抛弃了我们，意大利人忽视了我们
People are leaving us, Italians are ignoring us,
马其顿人提出的问题我们无法回答
Macedonians are asking questions to which we have no answer,
我们只能手挽着手坐着
and we are sitting arms crossed all the time
等待我们得不到的信号
waiting for a sign that we do not receive.
请不要生气，我可以问你一些事情吗？
Please don't be angry, can I ask you something openly?
我有种感觉...
I have a feeling...
你还指望我们吗？
Do you count on us at all?
好吧，我说清楚
Okay, I'll be clear.
像以前一样做事
Do everything as before.
不用担心钱的问题
And don't worry about the money.
克劳斯先生会帮你的
Mr. Klaus will help you.
计划是什么？
And the plan?
一切都按照我们的协议进行
Everything remains as we agreed.
你的工作是控制住 IMRO
Your job is just to keep IMRO under control.
- 时刻做好准备 - 谢谢
- And to be ready. - Thank you. That...
就这些了，谢谢你，帕夫里奇先生
That would be all, thank you Mr. Pavelich.
谢谢，再见
Thank you. Goodbye.
- 这是我在维也纳的电话号码 - 谢谢
- My phone number in Vienna. - Thank you.
再见
Bye.
和这些业余爱好者一起冒险是明智之举吗？
Is it smart to risk it all with these amateurs?
乌斯塔沙只是一个选择
Ustashas are just one option.
我们还有其他选择
We have others.
我们来看看哪个是最好的
We'll see which one is the best.
日沃因，把他们赶走！
Zhivoyin, scatter them!
走开！你干嘛盯着我看? ！
Come on! Why are you staring?!
快点，离开这里！
Come on, get outta here!
快点，快点！
Faster, faster!
一击致命
Straight to the heart.
这是用刀刺的
This was done with a knife.
这个伤口太大，不是刀
The wound is too big for the knife.
也许是刺刀？
Maybe a bayonet?
和巴雅克塔维奇一样？
As with Baryaktarevich?
这是什么？
What's that?
一个筹码...赌博用的
A chip... for big games.
这就解释了为什么法官会在这种地方
That explains why the judge is in a place like this.
他来赌博
He came to gamble.
纸上写的什么？
And the papers?
我不知道，一些签名
I don't know, some signatures.
我们以后再查
We'll check that later.
这是什么? ！
What's this?!
泽切维奇
Colleague Zechevich,
我认为我们光荣的法官
I think that our honest judge, God forgive his soul,
参与了一些不光荣的活动
was involved in not so honest actions.
如果我没有救你的命
If I hadn't saved your life,
亚得里亚海的鱼会吃了你
the Adriatic fish would be eating you.
如果我不带你出国
And if I didn't take you overseas,
两三天之内你就会死
you'd be dead in two or three days.
不管你藏在哪里，他们都会找到你
They would find you wherever you hid.
我告诉过你，我不在乎生命
I told you I didn't care about life.
我也告诉过你不要考验我的耐心
And I told you not to test my patience.
别把我当傻瓜，听听你要做什么
Don't make a fool of me. Listen to what you need to do,
去拯救那个你还在乎的生命
to save that life that you still care about.
你还能得到你梦想的工作
You'll also get your dream job.
我对毒品不感兴趣，托马斯维奇
I'm not interested in drugs, Tomasovich.
我对你们的商业政策也不感兴趣
I'm not interested in your business policy either.
如果你问我，你最好把她赶走
And if you ask me, you'd better get rid of her.
但你不会的
But you won't.
在那之前，你比任何人都更需要那毒品
Until you do, you'll need that drug more than anyone.
打扰一下！
Excuse me!
我的牛排没熟
My steak is undercooked.
我能换个新的吗？
Can I get a new one?
当然
Of course.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我不想当混蛋
Instead of being an asshole,
你应该亲我的屁股，因为我救了你的命
you should kiss my ass because I saved your life.
我帮你摆脱了那些人渣
And I got you out of the shit you played with.
我会给你找一份对他们来说很糟糕的工作
I'll get you a job that went so badly with them, that it can't be worse.
但你还不能管理它，干杯！
But you still couldn't run it. Cheers!
保加利亚边境 马其顿 德拉切村
Dramche village, Macedonia, Bulgaria border
小姑娘！
Little girl!
我不是小姑娘了，叔叔
I'm not a little girl, uncle.
我不是你叔叔
I'm not your uncle.
- 但你老了 - 老了? ！
- But you're old. - Old?!
- 你在这里干什么？- 你管我呢？
- What are you doing here? - Why do you care?!
基拉老板在哪里？
Where is boss Kyro?
他走了
He is gone.
怎么会？这里有管事的成年人吗？
How come?! Is there an adult?
没有，你要把一切都给我
No. You're going to give everything to me.
我能给你什么? ！
What can I give you?!
钱！
The money!
雅娜，放下枪
Yana, leave him alone.
爸爸，你毁了我的恶作剧！
Dad, you ruined my joke!
他不知道什么是恶作剧
He doesn't know what a joke is.
- 他来自亚塔汉贫民窟 - 哪里？
- He's from Yataghan slum. - From where?!
她是个危险的女孩，基拉老板
She's a dangerous girl, boss Kyro.
她将会取代你
She's about to replace you.
她很无聊
She's bored.
你只有一个女儿
You have a single female child
却把她带到这种地方
and you brought her in the middle of nowhere.
你来我这有什么好事？
What good brings you here?
谁说是好事了？
Who says it's good?
塔尼！等等！
Tane! Wait!
我赶时间！
I'm in a hurry!
好吧，我告诉你！
Okay, let me tell you something!
阿耳忒弥耶神父在找你，叫你去见他
Father Artemiye was looking for you and asked you to go him.
他找我什么事？
What did he want?
他说你知道什么事
He said you already know.
谢谢
Thanks.
你开始去教堂了吗？
Have you started going to church?
你还是有希望的
There's still some hope for you.
早上好，多布里沃耶
Good morning, Dobrivoye.
早上好，塔纳西耶维奇先生
Good morning, Mr. Tanasiyevich.
嘿，让我们单独待一会儿
Hey, leave us alone for a bit.
迪米特里耶维奇，怎么了？
What's up Dimitriyevich?
为什么要开这种秘密会议？
Why these secret meetings?
你怎么不在赌场？
Why aren't you at the casino?
再也没有赌场了，我要关门了
There's no casino anymore. I'm closing it.
所以我才给你打电话
That's why I called you.
是因为法官吗？
Is it because of the judge, huh?
那里发生了什么？
What happened there?
谁杀了他? 你知道些什么吗？
Who killed him? Do you know something about it?
不，但是我知道我有太多的事情要做
No, but I do know I have too much on my plate
不知道该怎么办
and don't know what to do.
他欠我一大笔钱
He owed me a huge amount of money.
他欠所有人的钱
He owed everyone.
我不在乎
I don't care about that.
他使我卷入了一桩肮脏的买卖
He got me into a dirty business.
我被耍了
And what a fool I turned out to be,
我还欺骗了我的儿子
I screwed my son over, too.
什么样的肮脏交易？
What kind of dirty business?
不重要，他一死就没生意了
Doesn't matter, the business failed as soon as he got killed.
也许在他死之前就没有了
Maybe even before that.
我打电话告诉你，你丢了工作
I called to tell you that you lost your job.
这就对了，我也骗了你
There you go. I screwed you over, too.
别担心，我会处理的
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
多布里沃耶，请帮我刮胡子！
Dobrivoye, shave me, please!
对不起
I'm sorry.
保重，迪米特里耶维奇
Take care, Dimitriyevich.
保重
Take care.
- 再见 - 再见
- Good bye! - Good bye!
南斯拉夫王国 贝尔格莱德 保罗王子的住所
Residence of Prince Paul, Belgrade, Kingdom of Yugoslavia
安德鲁，你变得更帅气了
Andrew, you've become even more beautiful.
你什么时候成了保罗王子的侍卫了？
Since when have you been in Prince Paul's guard?
差不多一年了，自从科罗沙克部长被捕以来
For almost a year. Ever since Minister Koroshac was arrested.
我就不能再为日瓦科维奇将军工作了
I couldn't work for General Zhivkovich anymore.
那个邪恶的人
That man is evil.
我们一直都认为他很邪恶
We have always agreed on that.
科罗沙克先生还好吗？
Is Mr. Koroshac fine?
他被软禁在家
As he can be, under house arrest.
真是了不起的人
Remarkable man.
他还没有说出他的最后一句话... 你会看到的
He hasn't said his last word yet... You'll see.
玛雅
Maya...
这种事不应该大声说出来..
Such things shouldn't be said out loud...
尤其是在这里
Especially not here.
即使是在朋友之间？
Not even among friends?
哦，我们只是朋友？
Oh, we are just friends?
现在是了，我结婚了
Now we are. I got married.
是的，我知道
Yes, I know.
好吧，你肯定不是来告诉我你结婚了
Okay, you certainly didn't come to let me know you are married.
我对你可能知道的事情很感兴趣
I'm interested in something I think you might know.
那个失踪的法国外交官诺维奇
That missing French diplomat Nowicki,
他本来要见国王的？
he was supposed to meet with the king?
我不能告诉你这些
I'm not allowed to tell you that.
你为什么想知道这些？
Why would you like to know that?
因为日瓦科维奇将军
Because of General Zhivkovich.
我听说他把事情搞砸了
I've heard he messed something up.
诺维奇正在安排那个试图说服我们殿下
Nowicki was arranging the visit of Minister of Foreign Affairs, Mr. Bartu,
承认苏联主权的
who was to convince our Highness that...
法国外交部长巴尔图先生来访
Yugoslavia should recognize the Soviet Union.
你知道幕后黑手是谁吗？
Do you have any idea who might be behind this?
对许多人来说，这个承认并不合适
For many, the recognition would not suit.
让我们从法国的极右派开始
Let's start from the French far-right parties,
然后那些德国，意大利的疯子..
then those lunatics in Germany, Italy...
然后是克罗地亚和马其顿的极端分子
and then our extremists in Croatia and Macedonia.
这个名单很长
The list is long.
好吧，安德鲁
Okay, Andrew.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你还说你结婚了？
And you got married, huh?
这么年轻，就已经是斯拉夫人了...
So young and already Slavic...
老鼠是凶手的标志
The rat is the killer's signature.
他用这种方式告诉我们受害者之间有联系
His way of telling us that the victims are connected.
他为什么把眼睛挖出来？
Why did he take out his eyes?
也许法官看到了他不该看到的东西
Maybe the judge saw something he shouldn't have.
法官伸张正义，正义是盲目的
The judge dispenses justice, justice is blind,
但也许对他来说，并不是盲目的
but perhaps in his case it was not blind.
我根本没想过
I didn't think about it.
我去查查他之前的案子也许能有所发现
I'll check his earlier cases, maybe I'll find something.
你脸上又有那种表情了
You have that look on your face again.
告诉我，怎么了？
Tell me, what's the matter?
- 我听说英国有个案子 - 什么案子
- I read about a case in England. - Okay.
谋杀妓女的案子
About the murders of prostitutes.
那个杀手是个宗教狂热分子
That killer was a religious fanatic
想要净化这个世界的罪恶
who wanted to cleanse the world of sin.
他割掉了妓女的生殖器和乳房
He cut the genitals and breasts of these women.
那是他的签名
That was his signature.
使命
Mission.
也许我们要找的人也有使命
Maybe our man has a mission.
也许你可以在睡觉前找些正常的东西来读
And maybe you can find something normal to read before bed.
我对这个很感兴趣
Well, I'm interested in this.
我看得出来
I can see that.
你需要多出去走走
You need to go out more.
这话是谁说的
Look who's talking!
我说的
I'm talking.
你不知道做这份工作是怎么回事
You don't know how it is to do this job.
这就是你来这里的原因
That's why you're here.
照顾我
To look after me.
我们需要知道那个法官的一切
We need to know everything about that judge.
查出他和谁在一起
To find out who he hung out with,
他做了什么事
what decisions he made,
他的经济状况如何... 一切信息
what was his financial situation... Everything.
- 好的 - 最重要的是
- Okay. - And most importantly,
他和那个不幸的矿工有什么联系吗
does anything connect him to that unfortunate miner.
普尔沙，我以后再付钱给你
Prsha, I'll pay you later.
我们把你送到这个世界是徒劳的，警察仍然是警察
In vain we send you into the world, the cop remains the cop.
- 索尼娅！- 你好 普尔沙
- Sonya! - Hello, Prsha.
我好几年没见过你了
I haven't seen you in years.
我只是路过
I just stopped by.
孩子怎么样了？
How's the kid?
他长大了，开始上学
He grew up, started school.
我给他带了点东西
I brought something for him.
谢谢你，不用这么客气
Oh, thank you, you shouldn't have.
你想进来喝一杯吗？
Would you like come in for a drink?
不，我赶时间
No, I'm in a hurry.
他还来这儿吗？
Does he still come here?
是的，他还来
Well, yes. He does.
你能帮我给他带个话吗？
Could you pass on one request to him?
当然可以
Of course I could.
我们应该见见面，这很重要
We should see each other. It is important.
如果他星期五能来这里
If he could come here on Friday,
- 在这个时间 - 好的，我会告诉他的
- at this time of the day. - Okay, I'll tell him.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
再见，普尔沙
Goodbye, Prsha.
好吧
Okay...
让我看看我把它放哪儿了...
Let me see where I've put it...
对不起，我想它... 在这里！
Excuse me, please. I think it's... Here it is!
正如我告诉你的，米特罗凡神父把手帐保存得非常整洁
As I told you, Father Mitrofan kept books very neatly,
他记录了所有的事情: 地点，时间,
he recorded everything: place, time,
日期，做了什么事...
date, what service it was...
让我看看，在这里
Let's see. Here it is.
安魂弥撒，1921年11月11日
So, requiem, 11th November, 1921.
- 名字呢？- 这就是问题所在
- And where's the name? - That's the problem.
看看这个
Look at this.
那一页被撕掉了
That page is ripped off.
为什么会有人这么做？
Why would anyone do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
谢谢你，神父
Thank you, Father.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
黑手党
The Black Hand.
就是在这里建立的
It was founded here.
1903年，一个解放所有塞尔维亚土地的中央委员会
In 1903, a central committee for the liberation of all Serbian lands
在这个避难所成立
was established in this sanctuary.
统一或死亡
UNIFICATION OR DEATH
我希望这个地方合你的口味
I hope this place is to your count's taste.
是的，是的，我爱这个地方
Yes, yes, I love this place.
我也是，我以前经常来这里
Me too. I used to come here a lot.
是这样吗？
Is that so?
玛雅，我们第一次一起来这里感觉很奇怪
Then it's weird that we're here together for the first time, Maya.
没有，因为我以前经常和朋友一起来
Not really, because I used to come with friends.
我喜欢你敏锐的幽默感，很少有女人有这种感觉
I love your sharp sense of humour, few women have it.
不，你被错误的女人包围了
No, you are surrounded by the wrong women.
聊正事吧
Let's get back to our problem.
我们组织的人
Someone from our organization
与维也纳总部保持直接联系
maintains direct contact with the headquarters in Vienna.
真的吗？
Really?
我对此一无所知
I don't know anything about that.
问题是我对此也一无所知
The problem is that I don't know anything about it either.
那可能是因为你离开了很长一段时间
That's because you've probably been away for a long time.
我不在，你怪我吗？
Do you blame me for my absence?
当然不
No, for God's sake,
我只是注意到你的缺席可能会带来一些后果
I'm just noticing that your absence could have some consequences.
例如，你的前任阿瓦库莫维奇
For example, your predecessor Avakumovich.
他每月至少召开一次组织会议
He held meetings of our society at least once a month.
要我提醒你我们是怎么纪念他的吗？
Should I remind you how we remember him?
是啊... 那些谋杀案
Yeah... All those murders.
还有你和你朋友克里斯塔的绯闻
And the affair with your friend Krista.
还有共匪戈卢比奇
And the red bandit Golubich.
我从来没有问过你，你有没有
I've never asked you, have you ever
再见到戈卢比奇？
had a chance to meet that Golubich?
没有
No.
跟这有什么关系吗？
What does it matter?
不要偏离主题
Do not deviate from the topic.
关于诺维奇伯爵的失踪你知道些什么？
What do you know about the disappearance of Count Nowicki?
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
你不知道他要来？
You didn't know he was coming?
我没那么说，我说我对他的失踪一无所知
I didn't say that. I said I know nothing about the disappearance.
如果那个人消失了
If the man disappeared at all.
除了国王，他还要...
Apart from the King, he was supposed to meet
- 和我们组织的人会面 - 和谁？
with someone from our organization. With whom?
玛雅，拜托，我说了我不认识那个人
Maya, please! I said I don't know that man.
我怎么知道他要见谁？
How could I know who he needs to meet?
我以为这会是一次愉快的谈话
I thought this would be a pleasant talk,
但很明显我错了
but I was obviously wrong.
关于矿山销售合同的事情，我们很快再谈
Talk to you soon about the contract for the sale of the mine.
我希望我们能尽快解决这个问题
I hope we'll resolve that quickly.
不! 不是那个! 我告诉过你把这个绑紧
No! Not that one! I told you to tighten this one.
- 不，你说的是这个 - 不，我说的是这个！
- No, you said this one. - No, I said this one!
- 我不能用这个扳手 - 我不能..
- I can't with this wrench. - I can't...
儿子，把大一点的扳手拿来
Son, bring me the bigger wrench.
- 萨夫卡! - 嘿！
- Savka! - Hey!
- 我带你去吃蛋糕吧 - 真的吗？
- Let me take you for a cake. - Really?
你这么瘦，却能打败那个大块头？
How are you so thin but you beat the big ones?
我有头脑和强壮的拳头
I have a brain and strong fists...
我还有个大东西要给你看
I have something big to show you.
真的吗？
Oh, really?
你是个硬汉
You're a tough guy.
- 西装不错 - 白色的
- Nice suit. - A white one.
- 萨夫卡! - 什么事？
- Savka! - Yes?
- 我们开个会 - 怎么了？
- Let's have a meeting. - What's wrong?
迪塞尔，管好你自己的事
Diesel, mind your business.
等等，让我带她去吃蛋糕
Wait, let me take her for a cake.
去你的蛋糕！
Fuck your cake!
看看今天的收益
Let's see the earnings for today.
今天怎么样？
How was it today?
看看那个混蛋
Look at that asshole.
他都爽上天了
He went too high.
闭嘴，把钱给我
Shut up and give me the money.
下午好！
Good afternoon!
塔尼，你好吗？
Tane, how are you?
- 哦，上帝，斯塔夫拉... - 赞内，把扳手拿来！
- Oh, God, Stavra... - Tzane, bring the wrench!
中尉夫人，很荣幸见到你
Mrs. Lieutenant, my respect.
难道没有男人为你做这些事吗？
Isn't there a man to do it for you?
这里没有男人，他们都没有能力
There's no man here, all of them are incapable.
别这么说，我上完了二年级呢
Don't say that Draginya, I finished two grades of school.
整整两学年？
The whole two?
好吧，只上了第二学期的两个月
Okay, just two months of the second.
你个废物
You have two left hands.
赞内，拿着扳手，把工作做完
Tzane, take the wrench to get the job done.
来吧，妈妈的傻孩子！
C'mon, mama's stupid boy!
- 傻逼，曼多夫 - 别逼我揍你！
- Suck my dick, Mandov. - Oh, don't make me do it!
中尉，你还在执行命令吗？
Lieutenant, you're keeping the order?
哦，亲爱的长官
Oh, dear Captain.
什么风把你吹到这个破地方来了？
What brings you to this shitty neighbourhood?
别这么说
Don't say that.
没有亚塔汉，就没有贝尔格莱德
There's no Belgrade without the Yataghan slum.
这是斯坦尼斯拉夫吗？
Is this Stanislav?
他长大了，不是吗？
He grew up, didn't he?
儿子，这是妈妈的战友
Andra, Mum's war friend.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
- 西装不错 - 白色的
- Nice suit. - A white one.
照顾好你的妈妈，工作愉快！
Take care of your mum. Happy work!
谢谢，孩子，到卡车下面去
Thanks. Son, go under the truck.
- 穿着白色西装? ! - 拜托，快点！
- In a white suit?! - C'mon, we have to do this!
你老板呢？
Where's your boss?
那要看是谁问了
Depends on who asks.
他在这等我
He's here for me.
如果你这么说的话
If you say so.
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
我来这里需要理由吗？
Do I need a reason to come?
不需要，但是你了解我，直接切入主题
No, but you know me, I get to the point right away.
我想你应该知道这是什么
I think you would know what this is.
你从哪儿弄来的? ！
Where did you get this?!
- 我们要喝什么? - 尼什基，出去
- What are we going to drink? - Nishky, out.
你要把我赶出我的酒吧
You're kicking me out of my bar.
别打架就好
Just don't fight.
这是阿皮斯的刺刀
This is Apis' bayonet.
我们用这把刺刀在每场战斗之前
We swore allegiance to each other over this bayonet
为了忠诚和奉献，互相宣誓效忠
before every fight, for loyalty and devotion.
它会在谁的手中结束呢？
In whose hands could it have ended?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许就在我们这些幸存者手中
Probably in hands of the few of us who survived.
说到这些，我听说戈卢布里奇在贝尔格莱德
Speaking of those, I heard Golubich is in Belgrade.
我不知道，我没看见他
I don't know. I didn't see him.
你不再给他提供武器了？
You don't get him weapons anymore?
没有
No.
当他需要我的时候，他就会找到我
When he needs me, he finds me.
你能告诉我
Could you tell me
我在哪儿能找到他？
where I could find him?
有一次他带我去他招募共产党员的地方
Once he took me to where he gathers his communists.
他们互相读马克思的著作
They read Marx to each other
说什么斯大林是个伟大的人
and talk shit about Stalin being a great man.
- 在哪儿? - 镇上的某个地方
- And where is that? - Somewhere up the town,
一片森林，郊区，有一个机器
some forest, suburbs. There's a machine.
什么机器？
What machine?
一个望远镜，像房子一样大！
A spyglass, as big as a house!
他们在那里看星星
They watch the stars there.
好吧
All right.
谢谢你，米兰
Thank you, Milan.
事情就是这样，亲爱的特纳瓦茨
That's the way it is, dear Trnavatz.
普里扎德拿走了所有东西
Prizad took everything.
罂粟田，工人，还有斯科普里的研究所
Poppy fields, processors, laboratory in Skopje.
路上到处都是警察
The roads are full of police, on every corner.
这就是为什么我们要跑到这里来
That's why we had to run here.
我看得出来
I can see that.
而且你也过得不是很好
And you're not doing very well either.
他夺走了整个贝尔格莱德的土地和道路
He took fields and roads from you, and from us - the whole Belgrade.
还有我丈夫
And from my husband, God took the brain.
现在他会夺走所有剩下的东西
Now he will take everything that's left.
如果我们不做点什么，一切都会分崩离析
If we don't do something, everything will fall apart.
- 我看得出来 - 你看得出来！
- I can see that. - You can see?!
如果你看出来什么，你就会把我弄出去
If you saw anything, you'd get me out of here.
- 这不容易 - 但却很容易骗到我？
- It's not easy. - And it was easy to fool me?
年轻时你欺骗了我，你这个老混蛋！
You tricked me young, you old jerk!
特纳瓦茨，你结婚了吗？
Trnavatz, are you married?
- 没结 - 千万别结
- God forbid, no. - Don't even try.
该死！
Dame!
基拉老板! 达米回来了！
Boss Kyro! Dame is here!
达米回来了！
Dame is here!
- 欢迎达米! - 达米！
- Welcome Dame! - Dame!
你好！
Hello!
雅娜！
Yana!
你长这么大了! 你不再是个小女孩了！
You grew up so much! You're not a little girl anymore!
我告诉过你我不是小女孩了
I told you I'm not a little girl.
基拉，这位是托马斯维奇先生
Kyro, this is Mr. Tomasovich.
丹尼洛，很高兴见到你，这是个小礼物
Danilo, nice to meet you. This is a little gift.
最好的法国白兰地
The best French cognac.
我只喝白兰地
I drink only brandy.
我们不和那些乌斯塔莎的混蛋
It's a good thing we won't work
混在一起是好事
with those Ustasha pricks anymore.
但是我们能力有限
But we certainly didn't do well
因为横跨大海的道路被切断了
because the road across the sea was cut off.
你有办法过海吗？
You have a way across the sea?
别担心
Don't worry about that.
我们在哪里给你送鸦片？
Where can we deliver opium to you?
不是鸦片，是海洛因
Not opium. Heroin.
什么? ！
What?!
海洛因
Heroin.
一种全世界都为之疯狂的新型毒品
A new drug that the whole world has gone crazy for.
你怎么把它从这里运走？
How will you transport it from here?
不用，我们会在这里生产
We won't. We'll produce it here.
你来制作，我来教你怎么做
You'll produce it, I will show you how to do it.
当我们成功的时候，我们的人会把它带去海上
When we make it, you and my people will take it to the sea.
你会得到比戈迪纳和帕维里奇更多的钱
You will get a lot more money than you did with Godina and Pavelich.
免得你觉得我是在胡闹或是耍你
And lest you think I'm fucking around and that I'm frivolous,
这是一小笔钱，作为善意的象征
here is a small amount, as a sign of good will.
不错，不错
Nice, nice.
什么事，维瑞加
Tell me, Veriga.
我只是想告诉你货已经到的里雅斯港口了
I just wanted to let you know the shipment has reached Trieste.
此乃天意
Only providence sent me Mr. Godina.
这种事情一辈子只做一次
Such work is done only once in a lifetime.
这将是我所有努力的结果
It will be the crown of all my efforts.
太好了，老大
Great, boss.
我所有的梦想...
All my dreams...
就会成真
will come true.
说到梦想
Speaking of dreams,
是时候让肮脏的梦想也成真了
it's time for dirty ones to come true.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
米拉丁卡，我们说到哪儿了？
Miladinka, where were we?
你看起来有点紧张
You seem a little tense to me.
真的吗？
Really?
你呢？
And you?
我从不紧张
I'm never tense,
这不在我的工作范围之内
that's not in my job description.
确实
That's logical.
这种逻辑是卑鄙的
The logic is mean.
就像你一样
Just like you.
你能不能告诉我
Would you please show me,
他们在舞台上是怎么刺你的？
how do they stab you on stage?
我已经告诉过你那是幻觉
I've already told you it was an illusion.
我知道
I know.
但是拜托...
But please...
我想成为幻象的一部分
I want to be part of the illusion.
来啊，求你了，刺我
Come on, please. Stab me.
不行，不是那把刀
I can't, it's not that knife.
- 刺我 - 不行
- Stab me. - I can't.
刺我
Stab me.
刺我！
Stab me!
- 哦，探长！- 你好
- Oh, Inspector! - Hello.
这是泽切维奇，我的新同事
This is Zechevich, my new colleague.
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you, too.
进来！
Come inside!
哇，你真的开始酗酒了！
Wow, you really drink!
从一大早开始是吧？
Since early morning, huh?
如果你戒酒了，并不意味着我不能享受生活
If you have stopped drinking, it doesn't mean I can't enjoy life.
坐下，孩子，你让我紧张
Sit down boy, you make me nervous.
你想喝点什么吗？
Would you like something to drink?
我不喝酒，谢谢
I don't drink, thanks.
来，坐下！
Come on, sit down!
从一大早开始你就紧张
You're nervous since early morning.
是的
I am.
因为是我让你把我卷进来的
Because I let you get me into this shit.
好了，别说了
Okay, don't start.
当我开始和贝尔格莱德的
I knew I was going to be fucked
半吊子警察合作的时候
when I started working with amateurs
我就知道我会被搞
from the fucking Belgrade police.
你要去哪儿，孩子？
Where are you going, kid?
这是不对的
This is not right.
这次谈话毫无意义
This conversation is going nowhere.
波兹达，过来，坐下
Bozidar, come on, sit down.
你这孩子给脸不要，是吧？
You're a cheeky kid, huh?
首先，我不允许任何人向贝尔格莱德警察抹黑
First of all, I do not allow anyone to spit on the Belgrade police.
我的名字是波兹达 · 泽切维奇
And my name is Bozidar Zechevich.
泽切维奇警官
Inspector Zechevich to you.
真的? ! 你说你是警官？
Really?! Inspector, you say?
是的
Yes.
所以聪明的警官大人，你也许知道
So when you are so smart, inspector, then you must know
被杀的那个人尸体不见了
where the body of the one who was killed on Zhrnov disappeared.
不见了？你在说什么？
Disappeared?! What are you talking about?
你不知道停尸房发生了什么事吗？
You don't know what's going on in your respectable Glavnjacha?
你从哪里得到消失的消息？
Where did you get the information that it disappeared?
我就是知道，波兹达
I just know, Bozidar.
我不是你这样正经的警官，但我知道
I'm not an inspector like you, but I know.
- 巴比奇告诉他的 - 是的！
- Babich told him. - He did!
我们想检查尸体上的纹身
We wanted to check the tattoo on the body,
但是没有尸体！
but there was no body!
别担心
Don't worry about it.
我们将用常规程序进行检查
We will check it with a regular procedure.
如果这是真的，巴比奇可能会为自己的行为负责
If it's true, Babich could be seriously held accountable for his actions.
你真的要把我惹毛了
And you could seriously piss me off.
塔尼！
Tane!
你给我好好说话
Change your tone.
他们肯定在停尸房做错了什么
They must have done something wrong in the morgue.
告诉我，神父告诉你什么了？
Tell me, what did the priest tell you?
死者的名字被记录下来了
The name was recorded. There was a name.
但有人把这页纸撕了下来
But someone ripped off the page.
好像他知道我们要去找似的
As if he knew that we were going to look for it.
那么这个名字可能也会出现在其他地方
Then that name probably appears somewhere else, too.
也许吧，阿特米耶神父也这么想
Probably. That's what Father Artemiye thinks, too.
但我不确定
But I'm not sure.
如果他真像你说的那么聪明
If he is as smart as you say,
他会试图抹去其他的痕迹
he'll try to erase the other traces.
我们会调查的
We'll investigate.
是的，你会调查
Yes, you'll investigate,
因为这是你的工作，不是我的
because it is your job, not mine.
看看法官是不是被这个杀死的
Check to see if the judge was killed with this.
你从哪儿弄来的? ！
Where did you get this?!
不重要，检查一下就行了
Doesn't matter, just check it.
你可以走了，我想睡觉
You can go, I want to sleep.
对不起
Sorry,
我没有别人可以借
I didn't have anyone else to borrow from.
我告诉过你我有钱，别担心
I told you I have money, don't worry about it.
- 你帮了我 - 你帮了我更多
- You helped me. - You helped me more.
当他们想要让我停业的时候
When they wanted to close my bar.
我不会忘记你是个好人
Prsha doesn't forget that, you're a man.
我会尽快还给你的
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
没事，给你
Take it easy. Here you go.
我在为我的儿子存钱，他刚上一年级
I was saving money for my son, he started school, first grade.
- 谢谢 - 上帝保佑你！
- Thanks. - God bless you!
上帝保佑你，阿尔忒弥耶神父! 你又来了？
God bless you, Father Artemiye! You've come again?
你好，塔纳西耶维奇今天来了吗？
Hello. Has Tanasiyevich come today?
还没有，但是他会的，他从来不会错过任何一天
Not yet, but he will, he never misses a day.
你可以坐着等他
You can sit and wait for him.
不行，我要去参加洗礼
I can't, I have a baptism.
你能让他来找我吗？
Can you tell him to come to me?
我们的塔尼成了一个虔诚的教徒吗？
Did our Tane become a religious man?
他经常去教堂
He's often at church.
我肯定他没有
I'm sure he didn't.
告诉他我发现了一些非常重要的东西
Tell him I've found out something very important.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
- 告诉他我知道那个名字了 - 名字？
- Tell him I know the name. - The name?
告诉他，他会知道的，谢谢，再见！
Just tell him that, he'll know. Thanks. Goodbye!
- 再见，神父 - 再见
- Goodbye, Father. - Goodbye.
你们到底想不想让我们拥有自己的国家，你们这些混蛋？
Do you want us to have our state or not, you motherfuckers?
你想坐在这里喝酒
You want to sit here, drink wine,
除了长胖就是做爱
to gain weight and fuck women.
妈的，我已经不做爱了
Dame, I don't fuck anymore.
你想让我们干你吗？
Do you want us to fuck you, Krume?
拿出你的武器，把那些刀磨快，准备好！
Take out your weapon, sharpen those knives and be ready!
达米安！
Damyan!
我们明天就要行动了！
We're going into action tomorrow!
看来你已经同意了
I see you've already agreed.
基拉，准备一间客房
Kyro, set up a guest house.
在我开始专心做事之前，我要睡一会儿
I'm going to get some sleep before I start minding my business.
确保你的生意不会影响我的生意
Make sure your business doesn't disturb mine.
我们井水不犯河水
My business - my thing, your business - your thing.
我们见面越少，就越不会打扰对方
The less we meet, the less we will bother each other.
我会处理的
I'll take care of that.
你是特纳瓦茨对吧？
Trnavatz, right?
- 没错 - 过来
- That's right. - Come here.
听着... 我想让你把我介绍给你的老板
Listen... I want you to introduce me to your boss.
- 什么老板？- 别来这套
- What boss? - Oh, give me a break,
我不会付钱给你的，你去跟裁缝说吧
you're not paid for that, announce me to the Tailor.
- 哦！普莱蒂科西奇! - 你好，普尔沙！
- Oh, Pletikosich! - Hello, Prsha!
忙完了吗? 我们去喝一杯吧！
Finished? Let's have a drink!
我很想去，但是警长在等我
I would like to, but the chief is waiting for me.
- 你看到塔尼了吗? - 看到了，怎么了？
- Have you seen Tane? - I have. Why?
牧师正在找他
The priest was looking for him.
他们已经见过面了
They've already met.
他又去找他了
He looked for him again.
他想要什么？
What did he want?
告诉他一个名字什么的
To tell him a name or something.
事情似乎很紧急，所以如果你见到他，请转告他
It seems to be urgent, so please tell him that if you see him.
我会的，谢谢
I will, thanks.
- 再见! - 再见，普尔沙！
- Bye! - Bye, Prsha!
嘿！
Hey!
我们必须去找塔尼
We have to go to Tane.
可是警长在等我们
The chief is waiting for us.
钥匙给你! 我想想办法
Here! I'll think of something.
波兹达！
Bozidar!
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 你要去哪里? - 晚上好
- Where? - Good evening.
我想参观天文馆
I would like to visit the planetarium.
可以吗？
Is that possible?
不行，有许可证才可以
No. Only with permission or announcement,
而且要明天白天再来
but you have to do it tomorrow, during the day.
这里有大望远镜吗？
Is there a big spyglass?
望远镜？
Telescope?
它在穹顶上，从这个灌木丛里看不到它
It's up on the dome, you can't see it from this bush.
谢谢，再见
Thanks. Goodbye.
塔尼！
Tane!
同志们！
Comrades!
马其顿有情况
We have a situation in Macedonia.
疯子阿尔索夫回来了
That crazy Hadzi Arsov is back.
我们该怎么办? 要我去那里吗？
What are we going to do? Want me to go there?
不，我会处理的，我没有叫你是因为他
No, I'll take care of it. I didn't call you because of him.
听着... 从现在开始
Listen... Every action,
所有行动，所有对政权的侵犯
every aggression towards the regime,
都必须马上停止
must stop immediately.
这次的命令是完全停止一切活动
The directive is a complete pacification.
明白了吗？
Is that clear?
我问你们明白了吗
I asked if it's clear.
对不起，菲利克斯同志，但是如果我理解正确的话
I'm sorry, Comrade Felix, but if I understand correctly,
- 我们必须停止一切活动？- 是的
- we must stop all activities? - That's right.
但为什么呢？
But why?
这是来自莫斯科的指示
It is a directive from Moscow.
但我们是在贝尔格莱德，不是在莫斯科
But we're in Belgrade, not in Moscow.
他们怎么知道这里发生了什么？
How do they know what's going on here?
他们当然知道，他们拥有所有的信息
Of course they know, they have all the information need.
也许他们有错误的信息
Maybe they have false information.
关在监狱里的不是苏联同志，而是我们的人民
It is not the Soviet comrades in Glavnjacha, but our people.
自从我党被取缔以来，我们的同志就被监禁了
Ever since our party was banned, our comrades have been imprisoned.
好了，闭嘴! 该死的！
All right, stop it! Goddammit!
你们怎么回事？我...我不明白
What's wrong with you?! I.. I don't understand you.
你们是不是想像那些马其顿的混蛋一样闹革命? ！
Are you playing revolutions like those jerks in Macedonia?!
同志们... 同志们，我不明白
Comrades... Comrades, I don't get it.
为什么听从莫斯科的指示是个问题？
Why is it a problem to listen to the directive from Moscow?
那我们应该听谁的命令呢？
Where should we listen to it from?
柏林? 伦敦？
From Berlin, huh? London?
如果有人不能理解这一点
If anyone has a problem understanding this,
我会亲自向他们解释的
I will personally explain it to them.
去吧，散会
Come on, you're free.
我们走吗？
Are we going?
坐下
Sit down, please.
别走来走去的，这使我心烦
Stop walking around, it annoys me.
我告诉你，她有些怀疑
I'm telling you, she has some doubts.
我也跟你说过，她什么都不知道
And I tell you she knows nothing.
坐下！
Sit down!
- 别担心 - 我不知道
- Don't worry. - I don't know.
我们正处在一个非常微妙的阶段
We're in a very delicate phase.
发生了一些我们一无所知的事情
Things happen that we know nothing about.
那些谋杀案！
All those murders!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
那些事情和达维多维奇夫人没有关系
Those things have nothing to do with Mrs. Davidovich.
她什么都不知道，在黑暗中摸索
She knows nothing. Searching in the dark.
你知道他们怎么说的: “每条狗都有它的一天”
You know how they say: "Every dog has its day."
伯爵..
Count...
你现在的问题只有诺维奇
your problem now is just Nowicki.
我来应付达维多维奇夫人
Leave Mrs. Davidovich to me.
什么事? ！
What?!
我告诉过你，如果有人找我，就说我不在家
I told you I wasn't home if anyone was looking for me.
对不起，但是很紧急
Sorry, but it's urgent.
失陪了
Excuse me.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
怎么会? ！
How?!
我明白了
I see.
把他赶走，马上
Get rid of him, now.
我很抱歉，但是你必须这么做
I'm sorry, but you'll have to.
这是什么意思? 你觉得呢？
What does this mean? What do you think?
我暂时没什么想法
Nothing for now.
- 晚安 - 晚安！
- Good night. - Good night!
你不留下来吗？
You're not staying?
不，今晚不行
No. Not tonight.
站住！
Stop!